School of the Museum of Fine Arts Records UA133
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Student Affairs records, circa 1876 -- 2016; UA133.005; 469.19 Linear Feet 388 record cartons; 5 card catalog boxes/10 drawers; 5 card boxes
  - 2018 accessions, 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.003; 426 Linear Feet 355 Record Cartons
    - Student folders, Liebman, Karen - Lindsley, Michel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.156 (Box 156)
    - Student folders, Lenge, Christopher - Lessmann, Alison, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.433 (Box 433)
    - Student folders, Lesson, Judith - Lew, Jennifer, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.165 (Box 165)
    - Student folders, Lewis, Anya - Lieberman, Justin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.173 (Box 173)
    - Student folders, Lindsay, Andrew - Litt, Rebecca, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.354 (Box 354)
    - Student folders, Little, Caitlin - Loheed, Shelley, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.192 (Box 192)
    - Student folders, Lohnes, Juiie - Lorie, Robert, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.254 (Box 254)
    - Student folders, Lorin, Lucy - Loyd, Meredith, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.099 (Box 99)
    - Student folders, Loyd, Meredith - Lye, Sinjin (St. John), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.184 (Box 184)
    - Student folders, Lye, St. John - Lyons, Steven, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.190 (Box 190)
    - Student folders, Maass, William - MacKenzie, Kenneth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.134 (Box 134)
    - Student folders, Mackenzie, Shannon - Magnell, Pamela, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.320 (Box 320)
    - Student folders, Magnarelli, Lisa - Majewski, Monika, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.257 (Box 257)
    - Student folders, Majkut, Katrina - Malone, Sherry, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.202 (Box 202)
    - Student folders, Maloney, Elizabeth - Manners, Boel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.102 (Box 102)
    - Student folders, Manni, Michael - Mapplebeck, Ann, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.256 (Box 256)
    - Student folders, Maracich, Joseph - Mark, Michael, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.255 (Box 255)
    - Student folders, Mark, Theodore - Marsh, Linn Ellen (Becker), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.341 (Box 341)
    - Student folders, Marson, Polly Ann - Martick, Lisa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.205 (Box 205)
    - Student folders, Martin, Judith - Maslo-Krkovic, Adaleta, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.178 (Box 178)
    - Student folders, Maslo-Krkovic, Adaletta - Matula, Sabe, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.258 (Box 258)
    - Student folders, Mature, Davone - McBride, Hilary, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.418 (Box 418)
    - Student folders, McBarron, George - McCoy, Timothy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.155 (Box 155)
    - Student folders, McCracken, Samuel - McGinn, Ryan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.259 (Box 259)
    - Student folders, McGinnis, Miranda - McKittrick, Norman, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.132 (Box 132)
    - Student folders, McKnight, Wendy - McMurray, Richard, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.199 (Box 199)
    - Student folders, McNabb, Patricia - Medeiros, Jared, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.260 (Box 260)
    - Student folders, Medeiros, Joseph - Mendenhall, Susan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.096 (Box 96)
    - Student folders, Mendes, Marta - Metcalf, Diana, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.261 (Box 261)
    - Student folders, Metcalf, Jason - Michel, Alan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.262 (Box 262)
    - Student folders, Michel, Nancy - Miley, Sarah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.435 (Box 435)
    - Student folders, Milholland, Peter - Miller, Katrina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.264 (Box 264)
    - Student folders, Miller, Kathryn - Milton, Christopher, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.263 (Box 263)
    - Student folders, Mims, Akiko - Mirza, Zareen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.265 (Box 265)
    - Student folders, Missbrenner, Kris - Modzelewski, Francis, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.266 (Box 266)
    - Student folders, Moe, Samantha - Monson, Kristen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.329 (Box 329)
    - Student folders, Monson, Patricia - Moore, Brennan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.267 (Box 267)
    - Student folders, Moore, Christine - Moran, Olivia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.161 (Box 161)
    - Student folders, Moran, Wendy - Morgenstern, Hayley, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.185 (Box 185)
    - Student folders, Morgenstern, Hillary - Morrisette, Gordon, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.271 (Box 271)
      Includes Cline, Hope and Follett, Carol
    - Student folders, Morrison, Donna - Moshfegh, Sarvenaz, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.168 (Box 168)
    - Student folders, Moskin, Nancy - Muir, Noel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.268 (Box 268)
    - Student folders, Muder, Rebecca - Elkins, Kelly-Ann, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.391 (Box 391)
      Original folder title was Student folders, Bud-Zyb; this box may contain folders from a wide alphabetical range.
    - Student folders, Muise, Nancy - Murphy, Caitlin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.269 (Box 269)
    - Student folders, Murphy, Charles - Murthy, Divya, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.270 (Box 270)
    - Student folders, Murton, Kimberly - Najarian, Suzanne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.298 (Box 298)
    - Student folders, Nakadate, Laurel - Nasonte, Sandra, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.342 (Box 342)
    - Student folders, Nassar, Josephine - Nelsen, Christine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.273 (Box 273)
    - Student folders, Nelson, Abigail - Newbury, Hester, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.274 (Box 274)
    - Student folders, Newcomb, Fred - Nichols, Webb, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.275 (Box 275)
    - Student folders, Nichols, William - Nikiforakis, Helene, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.157 (Box 157)
    - Student folders, Nirmalan, Anjali - Nordell, John, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.276 (Box 276)
    - Student folders, Nordlander, Theodore - Nunez, Katie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.410 (Box 410)
    - Student folders, Nunez, Alexandra - O'Connor, Megan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.167 (Box 167)
    - Student folders, O'Conner, Sharon - Oh, Connie (In-Young), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.421 (Box 421)
    - Student folders, O'Neil, Rebecca - O'Rourke, Logan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.439 (Box 439)
    - Student folders, O'Rourke, Logan - Osmer, Rylan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.344 (Box 344)
    - Student folders, Oh, Kyungha - Oliver, Barbara, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.277 (Box 277)
    - Student folders, Oliver, Kathryn - O'Neil, Lucinda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.426 (Box 426)
    - Student folders, Osorio - Buck, John - Oyler, Judith, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.416 (Box 416)
    - Student folders, Ozaeta, Maria - Paine, Barry, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.180 (Box 180)
    - Student folders, Paine, Robin - Palmacci, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.129 (Box 129)
    - Student folders, Palombo, Janice - Paredes, Maria, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.112 (Box 112)
    - Student folders, Parent, Kimberly - Parker, William, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.325 (Box 325)
    - Student folders, Parkins, Andrea - Patrick, Amanda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.278 (Box 278)
    - Student folders, Patila, Marrku - Paxton, Rachel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.370 (Box 370)
    - Student folders, Payne, Antony - Pelikan, Anne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.440 (Box 440)
    - Student folders, Pellagrini, Linda - Permar, Bradley, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.356 (Box 356)
    - Student folders, Pernas, Monica - Peterson, Arlayne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.174 (Box 174)
    - Student folders, Peterson, Carol - Pflugradt, Michele, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.136 (Box 136)
    - Student folders, Pham, Tung - Phungrasamee, Nicole, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.346 (Box 346)
    - Student folders, Piacenza, Valentina - Pillsbury, Sylvia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.441 (Box 441)
    - Student folders, Pimes, Julia - Pisera, Janina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.412 (Box 412)
    - Student folders, Pisharody, Anjana - Podles, Sarah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.347 (Box 347)
    - Student folders, Poe, Joan - Poole, Robert, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.357 (Box 357)
    - Student folders, Poole, Sidney - Potter, William, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.425 (Box 425)
    - Student folders, Pottle, Jill - Prendergast, Karen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.345 (Box 345)
    - Student folders, Prentis, Heath - Procopi, Nickolas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.182 (Box 182)
    - Student folders, Proctor, Martha - Pugh, Mark, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.198 (Box 198)
    - Student folders, Pugh, Sarah - Quental, Virginia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.361 (Box 361)
    - Student folders, Query, Joseph - Radochia, Kimberly, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.428 (Box 428)
    - Student folders, Radochia, Kimberly - Rapa, Christina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.422 (Box 422)
    - Student folders, Rapagnola, Andria - Reardon, Donald, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.200 (Box 200)
    - Student folders, Reardon, James - Regalado, Johanna, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.381 (Box 381)
    - Student folders, Regan, Judith - Repetti, Judith, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.103 (Box 103)
    - Student folders, Replogle, William - Rhoten, Deborah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.390 (Box 390)
    - Student folders, Ribeck, Nancy - Richmond, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.427 (Box 427)
    - Student folders, Richmond, Winifred - Ritter, Benjamin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.193 (Box 193)
    - Student folders, Ritter, David - Robertson, Mirion, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.183 (Box 183)
    - Student folders, Robertson, Rain - Rocheleau, Sarah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.349 (Box 349)
    - Student folders, Rochinski, Anna - Rodriguez, Nadia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.307 (Box 307)
    - Student folders, Rodriguez-Bosch, Noraida - Rollins, Edward, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.213 (Box 213)
    - Student folders, Rollins, John - Rosati, Flora, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.380 (Box 380)
    - Student folders, Rosato, Nicole - Rosenthal, Scott, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.362 (Box 362)
    - Student folders, Rosenvinge, Erica - Rossow, Christopher, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.324 (Box 324)
    - Student folders, Rostek, Jenny - Rozenman, Alexandra, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.289 (Box 289)
    - Student folders, Rubel, David - Rush, Timothy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.279 (Box 279)
    - Student folders, Rush, Todd - Ryan, Caroline, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.359 (Box 359)
    - Student folders, Ryan, Erica - Saeidian, Giti, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.350 (Box 350)
    - Student folders, Safajoo, Maryam - Salcedo, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.171 (Box 171)
    - Student folders, Salem, Gloria - Samyn, Fabrice, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.280 (Box 280)
    - Student folders, San Giacoma, Scott - Satenstein, Philip, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.308 (Box 308)
    - Student folders, Sanborn, Elisabeth - Sandy, Shani, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.311 (Box 311)
    - Student folders, Satiroglu, Aylin - Saxon, Elaine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.399 (Box 399)
    - Student folders, Saxon, Megan - Scheckman, Rebecca, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.396 (Box 396)
    - Student folders, Scheidt, Tyler - Schlumberger, Aurelien, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.294 (Box 294)
    - Student folders, Schlumberger, Helene - Schulenberg, Emily, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.393 (Box 393)
    - Student folders, Schulman, Alisa - Schultzerl, Melissa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.291 (Box 291)
    - Student folders, Schulz, Maja - Scott, Judith, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.369 (Box 369)
    - Student folders, Scott, Juliann - Segall, Sally, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.333 (Box 333)
    - Student folders, Segall, Tammy - Sereda, Jocelyn, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.409 (Box 409)
    - Student folders, Seronde, Jacques - Sharaya, Olexandra (Sasha), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.303 (Box 303)
    - Student folders, Sharet, Lynn - Shephard, Jennifer, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.317 (Box 317)
    - Student folders, Shepard, Kathryn - Shipps, Christine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.300 (Box 300)
    - Student folders, Shiraishi, Yoriko - Sibthorpe, Manali, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.316 (Box 316)
    - Student folders, Sichel, Gabrielle - Silverman, Ellen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.281 (Box 281)
    - Student folders, Silverman, Gessia - Sims, Kelli, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.315 (Box 315)
    - Student folders, Sims, Michael - Skowronski, Lorraine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.282 (Box 282)
    - Student folders, Skreta, Domnika - Smart, Roland, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.358 (Box 358)
    - Student folders, Smart, William - Smith, Henry, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.283 (Box 283)
    - Student folders, Smith, Holly - Smith, Samuel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.296 (Box 296)
    - Student folders, Smith, Sara - Snyder, Benson, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.297 (Box 297)
    - Student folders, Snyder, Brian - Solovei, Erika, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.327 (Box 327)
    - Student folders, Solovy, Steven - Sowa, Claire, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.293 (Box 293)
    - Student folders, Sowels, Deewayne - Spiegelman, Ben, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.414 (Box 414)
    - Student folders, Spiro, Ilona - Stancliff, Robin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.162 (Box 162)
    - Student folders, Stanfield, Jon - Staveley, Rebecca, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.299 (Box 299)
    - Student folders, Staveley-O'Carroll, Caitlin - Stevens, Elizabeth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.290 (Box 290)
    - Student folders, Stephenson, Claire - Stewart, Reba, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.302 (Box 302)
    - Student folders, Stewart, Susan - Stone, Betty, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.172 (Box 172)
    - Student folders, Stone, Caitlin - Stratton, Elizabeth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.304 (Box 304)
    - Student folders, Stratton, Kathryn - Styers, Dean, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.360 (Box 360)
    - Student folders, Styza, Samantha - Sullivan, Matthew, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.323 (Box 323)
    - Student folders, Sullivan, Melissa - Svoronos, Dennis, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.318 (Box 318)
    - Student folders, Swaim, Gavin - Szopa, Kristin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.310 (Box 310)
    - Student folders, Szpak, Laurann - Tammi, Mervi, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.288 (Box 288)
    - Student folders, Tamura, Marikka - Taswell, Margaret, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.365 (Box 365)
    - Student folders, Tatelbaum, Pamela - Tedford, Diane, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.326 (Box 326)
    - Student folders, Teer, Kelly - Thistle, Mary, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.131 (Box 131)
    - Student folders, Thomas, Antoine - Thurston, Meda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.355 (Box 355)
    - Student folders, Thurlow, Robert - Tobin, Christine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.177 (Box 177)
    - Student folders, Toby, Saul - Torrey, Jesse, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.408 (Box 408)
    - Student folders, Toscano, Kristen - Travers, Kara, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.377 (Box 377)
    - Student folders, Travis, Howard - Tsai, Ying-Hsin (Cindy), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.395 (Box 395)
    - Student folders, Tsal, Esti - Turgeon, Rita, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.376 (Box 376)
    - Student folders, Turiello, Patrick - Unrau, Tristan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.284 (Box 284)
    - Student folders, Untz, Stephanie - Vanderpoel, Nicole, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.430 (Box 430)
    - Student folders, Vanalystne, Meghan - Varani, Hannah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.413 (Box 413)
    - Student folders, Vardas, Angel - Venus-Murmann, Catharina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.305 (Box 305)
    - Student folders, Venus-Murmann, Catharine - Vieira, Richard, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.285 (Box 285)
    - Student folders, Vieira, Victoria - Vlahos, George, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.397 (Box 397)
    - Student folders, Vo, Tho - Wadsworth, Eliza, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.366 (Box 366)
    - Student folders, Wagg, Yana - Walker, Steven, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.306 (Box 306)
    - Student folders, Walker-Sefter, Jai - Walter, Sophie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.312 (Box 312)
    - Student folders, Walters, Theodore - Ware, Rene, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.388 (Box 388)
    - Student folders, Warhall, Mark - Waters, Richard, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.286 (Box 286)
    - Student folders, Waters, William - Webber, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.375 (Box 375)
    - Student folders, Weber, Christina - Weinraub, Linda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.437 (Box 437)
    - Student folders, Weinstein, Adam - Welch, Omari, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.417 (Box 417)
    - Student folders, Wells, Annelizabeth - Werthan, Sidney, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.403 (Box 403)
    - Student folders, Wesbecher, Kate - Whipple, Stacey, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.401 (Box 401)
    - Student folders, Whitaker, Linda - Whitten, Diana, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.371 (Box 371)
    - Student folders, Whitten, Diana - Wilkinson, Sandra, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.429 (Box 429)
    - Student folders, Will, Lisa - Williamson, Sarah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.438 (Box 438)
    - Student folders, Williamson, Sarah - Witham, Justin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.337 (Box 337)
    - Student folders, Wingert, Judith - Wojcik, Deborah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.387 (Box 387)
    - Student folders, Wojcik, Deborah - Wong, Timothy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.432 (Box 432)
    - Student folders, Woo, Bongsik - Woods, James, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.287 (Box 287)
    - Student folders, Wootten, Matt - Wu, Kaity, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.436 (Box 436)
    - Student folders, Wu, Mong (Jane) - Yamamoto, Mikoto, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.379 (Box 379)
    - Student folders, Yamamoto, Tamotsu - Yu, San Man, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.368 (Box 368)
    - Student folders, Yates, Gregory - York, Lindsay, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.400 (Box 400)
    - Student folders, York, Yvonne - Yuen, Sue Yan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.405 (Box 405)
    - Student folders, Yudin, Pam - Zelesny, Carol, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.319 (Box 319)
    - Student folders, Zelkind, Stefanie - Zingaro, Alice, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.373 (Box 373)
  - 2021 accessions, 1893 -- 2016; UA133.001816
    75 years from date of creation.
    Transferred by Colin Buckley, Student Services Coordinator, 2021, accession UA-2022-017.
    This series is arranged in received order.
    - BFA and MFA student and diploma advising files and leave of absence and withdrawal forms, 2009 -- 2016; UA133.001817 (Box 607)
    - MFA incomplete students and BFA and combined degree advising files, 2010 -- 2015; UA133.001818 (Box 608)
    - Leave of absence and withdrawal forms, transfer credit evaluations, and continuing education grade sheets, 1998 -- 2013; UA133.001819 (Box 609)
    - Gift records and Tufts + Master of Arts in Teaching records, 1950 -- 2005; UA133.001820 (Box 610)
    - Student affairs records, 1970 -- 1989; UA133.001821 (Box 611)
    - Grade sheets and evaluations, 1991; 2005 -- 2010; UA133.001822 (Box 612)
    - Grade sheets and evaluations, 1979 -- 1982; UA133.001823 (Box 613)
    - Grade sheets and evaluations, 1977 -- 1979; UA133.001824 (Box 614)
    - Grade sheets, 1983 -- 1992; UA133.001825 (Box 615)
    - Course descriptions and class schedules, grade sheets, and faculty and student handbooks, 1968 -- 2007; UA133.001826 (Box 616)
    - Curriculum Committee, courses and curriculum records, and enrollment statistics, 1960 -- 2010; UA133.001827 (Box 617)
    - Student Affairs records, 1971 -- 2010; UA133.001828 (Box 618)
      Enrollment statistics and policies, course schedules and descriptions, workshop descriptions, grade sheets, High School Honors program records, and correspondence.
    - Pro Arts records, 1987 -- 1992; UA133.001829 (Box 619)
    - Grades, rosters, and reviews, 1960 -- 1986; UA133.001830 (Box 620)
    - Commencement records and lists of graduates, 1893 -- 2006; UA133.001831 (Box 621)
    - Tufts + Master of Arts in Teaching, high school honors, and grade sheets and evaluations, 1975 -- 2004; UA133.001832 (Box 625)
    - Continuing Education portfolio evaluations, A-D, 1968 -- 1981; UA133.001833 (Box 623)
    - Continuing Education portfolio evaluations, D-G and W-Z, 1968 -- 1981; UA133.001834 (Box 624)
    - Continuing Education portfolio evaluations, H-M, 1968 -- 1981; UA133.001835 (Box 622)
    - Continuing Education portfolio evaluations, N-V, 1968 -- 1981; UA133.001836 (Box 626)
    - Tufts course reviews, 1988 -- 1990; UA133.001837 (Box 627)
    - Course descriptions, class schedules, and publicity, 1969 -- 1990; UA133.001838 (Box 628)
    - Class rosters and grades, 1947 -- 1985; UA133.001839 (Box 629)
    - Part-time student evaluations, committee meeting minutes, and administration and faculty correspondence, 2007; 1978 -- 1989; UA133.001840 (Box 630)
    - Grade sheets, 1991 -- 1997; UA133.001841 (Box 631)
    - Grade sheets, 1998 -- 2002; UA133.001842 (Box 632)
    - Class rosters, grade sheets, incomplete contracts, and MIT, continuing education, and summer school information, 1958 -- 1999; UA133.001843 (Box 633)
    - Grade sheets and course reviews, 1981 -- 1990; 2008; UA133.001844 (Box 634)
    - Pro Arts forms, Commencement records, and graphic design certificates, 1990 -- 2010; UA133.001845 (Box 635)
- Dean's Office records, circa 1979 -- 2010; UA133.006; 1.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains records from the Dean's Office dating from the 1940s to 2016. These records include annual school budgets, commencement speeches and programs, correspondence, handbooks, memos, and reports created by the Dean's office. There are also records of art and books loaned to the Museum of Fine Arts as well as records of art sales through Christie's auction house.
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
  - Correspondence, memos, commencement speeches, and handbooks, circa 1979 -- 2010; UA133.006.067 (Box 67)
  - Budgets, handbook, reports, exhibition material, circa 1995 -- 2010; UA133.006.060 (Box 60)
- Development records, circa 1987 -- 2016; UA133.007; 12.58 Linear Feet
  This series contains records from the Development office dating from circa 1987 to 2016. These records include event publicity material and photographs; commencement files; correspondence; and reports. The Development Office also encompasses Alumni Relations. Alumni Relations material includes artists' slides, photographs, and correspondence. The Arts Cheerleaders were a performance organization founded by SMFA students in 1995 under the name SFMA Cheerleaders and revived by alumni in 2007 in Virginia under the name Arts Cheerleaders. The organization raised awareness for arts education, and their records include clippings, correspondence, drafts of cheers, performance calendars, performer audition sheets, photographs, and a scrapbook. Related Arts Cheerleaders materials can be found in Series 5: Student Affairs records.
  - Alumni Relations: Artist slides, correspondence, and exhibition materials, circa 2000 -- 2010; UA133.007.038 (Box 38)
  - Alumni Relations: Slides and photographs; artMatters; and commencement slides, circa 1996 -- 2003; UA133.007.035 (Box 35)
  - Alumni slides, Art Cheerleaders records, and media files, circa 1996 -- 2015; UA133.007.045 (Box 45)
    One folder relating to employee records is closed for 75 years. Four folders pertaining to media contracts are closed for 20 years. The rest of the box is open for research.
  - Arts Cheerleaders clippings, 2007; UA133.007.026 (Box 26)
  - Artist slides H-R, circa 2000 -- 2010; UA133.007.042 (Box 42)